A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, David Rockefeller family Financial records FA1362
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller papers, David Rockefeller family Financial records
1916-1979
1940-1969
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Peggy
FA1362
31.44 Cubic Feet 8 transfile boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of select David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller cashbooks, contributions, ledgers, household account books, farm account books, business account books, receipts and disbursements, expenditures, trial balances, and securities.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
- David Rockefeller Farm Account Cashbook No. 1, 1950-1958 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account Cashbook No. 2, 1958-1961 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Business No. 2, 1957-1959 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Business No. 3, 1959-1960 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Business Cashbook, 1940-1946 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Household Account No. 1, 1951-1957 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Household Account No. 2, 1958-1965 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller Household Account No. 3, 1966-1972 (Box T4)
- David Rockefeller General Ledger No. 4, 1968-1969 (Box T13)
- David Rockefeller Distribution of Expenditures (Box T13)
- David Rockefeller Business Account, 1948-1949 (Box T13)
- Special Farm - Wartime Project, 1942-1946 (Box T13)
- Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1956-1958 (Box T13)
- Abby Rockefeller Cashbook - Account No. 2, 1964-1969 (Box T13)
- David Rockefeller Business Account No. 1, 1946-1947 (Box T13)
- David Rockefeller Business No. 4, 1960-1961 (Box T13)
- David Rockefeller Children Cashbook, 1970-1972 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller 1975 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Family - 1974 Accounting Detail Report (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account - 1970 Trial Balances (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller, David Rockefeller Farm Account - 1971 Trial Balances (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller - 1976 Trial Balances and Cash Receipts (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account - 1975 Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Accounting Detail (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Family Securities Reports, 1970-1972 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller - Securities, Transactions, and Schedule D, 1979 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller Family Funds and Corporations - 1973 Copperfield Fund, Atlanta Investing, Claymark Corp., Dekalb Investing, Jericho Bay - Tartan Bay, Inc. (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Family - Contributions, Donations and Presents, 1974 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Family - Contributions, Donations and Presents, 1976-1979 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller and Family - 1972-1973 - Year End Accounting Details (Box T24)
- Cashbook - David Rockefeller, Peggy Rockefeller, Farm Account, 1970-1972 (Box T24)
- David Rockefeller, Peggy Rockefeller, and Family - Contributions, Donations and Presents, 1971-1972 (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller 1974 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Securities, and David Rockefeller Farm Account - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller 1973 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Securities, and David Rockefeller Farm Account - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account 1976 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Accounting Detail (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller Farm and Estate Account 1977 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Account Detail (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller Farm and Estate Account 1978 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Account Detail (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller - Securities, Transactions, and Schedule D, 1975 (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller - Securities Inventory, 1970-1972 (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller 1974 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements (Box T22)
- NAR Farms, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller Family Funds and Corporations - 1978-1979 - Atlanta Investing, Claymark Corp., Copperfield Fund, DeKalb Investing, Panfair (Box T22)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account - General Ledger No. 1, 1961 (Box T6)
- David Rockefeller Securities, Stocks No. 1 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1968-1969 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller (MMcGR) Cashbook, 1958-1963 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook, 1963-1968 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook No. 4, 1969-1970 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook, 1940-1954 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Ledger - Investment Book, 1941-1952 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller General Ledger, 1965 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Journal - Investment Account (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Journal - Investment Account, 1953-1962 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Journal - Investment Account, 1953-1960 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Ledger (appears to be empty) (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Ledger, 1953-1958 (Box T6)
- Peggy Rockefeller Ledger No. 2, 1959-1964 (Box T6)
- David Rockefeller General Ledger No. 2, 1964-1965 (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller General Ledger No. 3, 1966-1967 (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller Ledger Business, 1947-1949 (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller Journal, 1916 July-1946 August (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller Personal Account, 1940-1941 (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller Household Account, 1940-1946 (Box T47)
- David Rockefeller General Ledger No. 1, 1963 (Box T3)
- Peggy Rockefeller No. 1 - Cashbook, 1970 (Box T3)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook, Investment Account, 1946-1952 (Box T3)
- Peggy Rockefeller Cashbook No. 1, 1953-1958 (Box T3)
- David Rockefeller - Business Cashbook, 1950-1951 (Box T3)
- David Rockefeller - Business Cashbook, 1952-1953 (Box T3)
- David Rockefeller - Business Cashbook, 1954-1955 (Box T3)
- David Rockefeller - Business Cashbook No. 1, 1955-1957 (Box T3)
- David Rockefeller Farm Account - Ledger, 1950-1961 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Journal - Deductible Expenses and Taxes, 1956-1957 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Journal - Deductible Expenses and Taxes, 1958-1959 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Journal - Deductible Expenses and Taxes, 1960 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Journal - Business Accounts, 1961 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Journal - Farm Account, 1946-1960 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Ledger - Farm Account, 1946-1949 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Contributions, 1936 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Farm, 1946 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller, 1946-1947 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller, 1940-1942 (Box T8)
- Peggy Rockefeller (Margaret D) (Box T8)
- Trial Balances - David Rockefeller and Peggy Rockefeller, 1954-1959 (Box T8)
- Household Account, David Rockefeller Personal, Peggy Rockefeller Personal, Record of Accounts in connection with Budget, 1949-1950 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Household, Peggy Rockefeller Personal, 1950-1951 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Household Account, 1947-1950 (Box T8)
- David Rockefeller Family - Cash Receipts, 1968-1969 (Box T9)
- David Rockefeller Farm - Index (Box T9)
- David Rockefeller Business (Unlabeled) (Box T9)